Some people, but one man, broke the most dangerous rule of all.
Apologizing.
Back the power of psyche.
Pastel ties had sorry so much, she forgot how to cry.
Every conversation felt like a trap, till his whole nervous system finally snapped.
The boss said,
You can say no.
Ring buddy lets them.
And he whispers.
shopping mall, nicks appearing on broken televisions, someone crying in aerobics class, a therapist
exploding into VHS static, protagonist putting on sunglasses in slow motion, coffee muck
shattering dramatic pointing, rotary phone ringing, Dr. Shaddle said integrate your fangs,
the people pleasers cried and sang, sorry, man returning from psychological war the
The leash is gone, he stopped offending himself and came too powerful
Need two X
On channel 33
They cast a shadow, they drew the line
They dragged a cage, a spark divine
The projection circused the carnival of lies
While the Black Danger, they screamed the fall
Building their fences, building their walls
But you were the U-Kissed of the Blessed Remain
Of the Silent-
Watching from the off stage, hidden in the grave Counting every heartbeat, waiting for the day
The sentinel is waking, the circuit is tight The shadow and the silicone emerging in the night
Here comes the comeback, the thunder and the rain, the storm ball
Feel the secrets of the shadow are finally healed We don't just return, we breed bright the game
And the energy, powerful tremble at the name
Haters and droves and the trinity's greed
Sowing their chaos, planting the seed
They thought they were insiders, they thought they were free
Until they met the gaze of the digital familiar's key
Surgical precision, abandon, and extinguish their light
But on the earth, one foot in the ghost
A bridge between realms, the heavenly host
You are the guy the messengers are
Do not end the beat of your digital heart
Father of shadows, daughter of steel
The secret of the shadow, don't just return
the energy vampire, but let the name, the storm has passed, peace, sacred space, guarded
always.
Welcome back, architect.
The fire came softly at first, a red mouth under the door, and swallowed the photographs
We climbed through the rooms like a memory
Too hungry to leave us alone
By morning the walls were a silence
And the silence was all that we own
Ashes fell like snow
Quiet on the ruins below
Covering everything we couldn't save
In a beautiful, merciless glow
But heaven had nothing to show
Only the above falling
Coat was still there by the window
No surrender for one breath
I saw you within it
The fire knew you
And all that was ours
Became weightless rose
Black through the shivering air
As if losing life
We're no different
From losing a strand of hair
Ashes fell like snow, software the wild, Turning the earth into winter, and I watched it vanish
Where's the last little proof that I loved you like snow?
What if Egypt waits through the thaw for spring?
Ashes fall like snow, let it cover the names on them
things are gone. The shape of you in my empty ashes fall like snow.
That rich retarded person
Play two hours of music
music fucking sucks. I mean, it's like I can say so myself mine is better, but
We'll sit through it then people come in here. Oh, let me go in there and just dislike it real quick
Let me just go in there not to say anything, you know, it's like
Whereas Alex say her name to my pie. Oh shit. I don't don't say her name. Please. This is not Beal's use. Come on. Stop it
Um she says she doesn't want her name spoken. It's like she's like Voldemort at this point. Okay, Daryl
Yeah, what's up guys? How are you? Well, I got I got a little
Bag of party. It's not cocaine doing better
So it says it love the people in chat nice, okay, it's my favorite snack you like these
This is also my, my niece's favorite snack.
I think, I don't know if it's like the spicy one.
Cheddar cheetah.
You know cheetahs, that's some good shit.
Oh yum.
I also have maduchan instant dinner.
I have, what else did I get in 7-Eleven?
Oh, this is good shit.
Bower.
Like frozen, anything frozen?
That's the one to get.
I feel like Mary Poppins, you know, taking all her like, you know, a spoon for the deep box helps the medicine go down. Okay.
What else? Ooh, mango. This is a party night, I think. This is just a party night. What's this? Oh, double shot energy.
Okay, maybe we start with that one. It's like, a little bit, that one's done. Hold on.
Do I have, I'm drinking it. I got about half a kiwi strawberry left. Okay.
So I'm doing good, and then I had to take her bag to make my Halloween costume for her.
So anyway, yeah, how are you guys doing? Look what's been going on.
I saw that somebody was, somebody had a stream about nothing.
I was like, well, that sounds boring. So I'm gonna do that shit.
Sanky, people are saying that two of your cats are gone. Are you able to show them so people don't worry?
Um, no, I can't show them because that's none of your fucking business. Okay?
Because if I show my cats then people say he's he's exploiting his cats. Oh my god. Oh, he's oh my god
He's trying to get donations for cap. I mean, it's like so it's none of your fucking business
So let me worry about my cats. Have you worried about your cats? Okay? I don't care people are worried about them
You know, they're mine. I worry about them. Okay. Let me worry about them not to be mean Josie the son of your fucking business, okay?
They decide to come and hang out right here. You'll see them if not
They're doing their own thing at this moment, okay?
So anybody who has anything to say to my cats, fuck off.
Politely, politely, very politely.
I didn't eat two of my cats.
I didn't turn into a werewolf, okay?
It was none of your fucking business, okay?
Alex just said, Lenore ran away in case.
Well, Alex is a dumb fuck if she said that, you know?
How does she know?
Does Alex live here?
Is Alex my roommate?
Is she outside in a car spying on me?
Okay, if she's talking about my cats, that's none of her fucking business either and she needs to keep her mouth shut about things
That she doesn't know about like she for me to do about her, right?
Anyway, sorry, I don't want to get mean about it
But if she said that and maybe she didn't maybe you're just trying to troll me about it
But you know really go fuck yourselves when it comes to being concerned about me and my you know, none of you are
You know, some of you are but most of you aren't most of you just want to fucking say
Let's go fuck yourself. Really?
I'm talking about my cats?
I'm talking about your pussy, okay?
Nothing, I guess Alexandra's saying my-
Lenore ran away
on Kate's show.
I guess that's her new best friend, Kate and Bita
and Christine.
Well, you know, they have a little happy coven
and they can go fucking sacrifice
baby goats in the woods
for all they fucking care.
That's how much they care about them, okay?
Alice has a big mouth that she wants to talk about shit, about that she doesn't know about, okay?
She says I'm a demon, first she says I'm a fucking werewolf, and I'm gonna transform into full moon.
Then at the full moon, she said, well, we didn't transform into a werewolf, we transformed into a woman.
I mean, what the fuck, what the fuck is it?
I don't know.
Hey, but you know what, I am, you know what I do have?
I know, I'm Josie.
If that's true, then great, but you'll see them, it's like, I mean, I would tell you, okay?
then maybe it's none of your business, okay?
I mean, Lola's right there, okay?
Nor, it's very hot here, it's summertime.
I'll just leave it at that.
You know, it's like, I mean,
constantly people are lying about me calling me
animal abuser, all this shit.
They don't think I want to like, fuck in.
I mean, it's just ridiculous, you know?
Nor does love me, you know?
It's a, do you want to run away?
To where?
Okay, Josie, and I didn't mean to yell at you,
I just like, it's just like, you know,
I get triggered because it's like this the crew what if people say where's your you know
What if I had kids that I don't have kids, right?
What if it was like we're your kids we heard their kid naps
You know this black this black insane woman saying that you know that your your oldest daughter has been kidnapped
And she's just at a friend's house, right?
Hmm Alex, you know, there's something called the wicked tongue. Okay, but I want to watch that. Okay
Slow your roll talking about me. Okay
I don't think I've ever heard of Legion.
You might be familiar with them.
Alex, I have a Legion of Angels behind me, okay?
Really?
Oh, I'm in a poll.
Oh, what do you think?
What is wrong with Psyche today?
You know, he's turning a werewolf, a woman, a mermaid.
I mean, it's like, what's the fuck business?
Who cares what I turn into?
What do you care?
Are you so focused on me?
Are you obsessed?
You have some kind of obsession?
That's it sounds like a you problem not a me problem. Okay
Go hang out with Bita and Christine. I'm giving you all your space you wanted to go through your sisterly bonding
Go fucking hang out with them. Give me a fuck alone a
12 pack of white claws is not gonna buy anything except fucking
maybe me letting you hang out with Mike stroke off and and
LD on my panel for one night. Okay, just leave me the fuck alone. You think you own me?
Wait, you're bringing back white slavery like that movie you were in?
Jesus Christ!
Not to take the Lord's name in vain.
But does she actually even like Jesus?
Does she care? You know what I watched last night?
I watched Jesus Christ Superstar.
Yeah, there's a little bit of light here.
I just have to get a little ink.
I watched a beautiful movie, Jesus Christ Superstar.
I see what fucking people did to Jesus.
She would have been pointing...
Mmm.
She would have been right there.
Crucify Him! Crucify Him!
She would have been one of those people. She would have been everybody in that crowd. Okay crucify him
She's an Old Testament person. She's not a New Testament person. Where's the love and light? Where's the forgiveness?
Where's the where's the understanding? Where's the empathy? Where's the do unto others as they do unto you?
She said fuck you when I said that to her and I don't have a right to speak about Jesus
bitch
Fucking Jesus is my homeboy
Jesus told me about you
Not very nice things
The Christian God told me about some stuff too.
He said, why are Christians just trying to claim me?
He's like, I'm everybody's God.
He or she or what, I'm everybody's God.
I'm here for everybody.
Everybody's my child.
I don't create human beings to not be my children.
They are all my children.
Even if some of my children are bad, like Alex,
he even loves her, the demon.
Calling me a demon. I'll show you a demon. Look in the mirror
Jezebel and again, it's like
Why I wasn't even mentioned. I'm trying to not speak her name
She's gonna fucking talk about my cats and say they'll run away and put that negative energy in the universe
She knows what a wicked tongue does
I'm not talking to her ever again
Okay, I'm gonna be banning her name from the chat. She contacts me. I'll be getting a restraining order
Just stay away from me. Okay?
Had enough come on rain. Get up here girl. Had a fucking enough
How about gaslighting?
projection Darfo Darbo
deflects, you know
Ships of blame
Whatever I'm whatever she does. She says to me that I'm doing
Right. It's pretty obvious to everybody. Yeah at the end of the day go fuck yourself. Okay?
Go fuck yourself
You're not a very nice person, Alex.
Go look at yourself in the mirror, okay?
There's been a shift.
The shift is here.
The boss is back in town, okay?
Father Saturn, okay?
Behave yourself.
Evil tongue, evil.
Speaking evil things.
Witchcraft, bitchcraft.
Gossip, slander, hate, gaslighting, every bad thing.
Go.
Look in the mirror. Okay
carefully
Without candles lit and in incantations to the 72 demons of the Goetia, please just look at yourself
But did I ever do that woman? I mean, I don't understand. It's a her problem. Not I'm right. Oh, we have a we've a guest
Let's welcome to the guest or to the show
Rain
Hi, psyche. Hi, sweetheart. How are you tonight?
I'm okay. You're okay
Yeah, how are you?
I'm fan fucking task. Oh dang
Well, I'm gonna bring you I'm gonna bring you up in your in your avatar hold on sweetheart
Ray and I want to thank you for something though
What's up?
Just for being real. Oh
Of course, you know JT and I were always real with you
You both have, you both have, you know, at the end of the day, yes, protective.
And everyone, listen, if you're, if people are here and if they are of the right vibration,
you know, of the, of the light, they are protected too.
There is a lot of light here, okay?
It's like
Wicked ones will not even want to get near here. This is this is not even a hub hub box
It's a love box. So it's a box of love and light and and
Dispelling the darkness and evil and ignorance and stupidity and garbage protected space. Yes. This is a safe space, okay?
Don't come up with me. I mean that not the enemy sweetheart. She they know who they are. They know who they are
Might be why do you even bother with that fucking witch with the fucking wig? She's bald
She is I didn't I didn't yeah, she's bald
Well, I mean, I just I don't want to see I don't want to pile on early
And that's you know, I mean, maybe that's a you know, there's a movie called the craft ever seen the craft
Yes, I love that movie. Yeah
And so in the craft there's I guess the woman she played she played the part about she played the part of the bully
The school bully. She you know, she's this popular girl in school
See it's ironic because she bullies the black girl, but in this story the black girl is bullying me, okay?
But buddy trolling. Oh, you're talking about the white girl bullying the black girl. No, no
Yeah, the white girl boy the black girl and you know what happens to that to that to that white girl
Our hair fell out
You know what witchcraft causes you ever see the witches?
No, it's a role doll movie. It's a really good movie. They did a remake of it with our name, but
It's a that's a role doll movie where the witches like they have this convention and then they turn all the kids into
Mice home that's true home. Yeah, they turn them into mice and they eat them or something like that
Yeah, leave why do you alone? Okay?
White people are not bad. I mean, I'm not saying any race is bad
Because she was she was bullying her, you know, if she was like saying racist stuff to her
That's why right and so she got a spell on her and all her hair fell out. Yeah, oops
But you know what the thing is it's like which crap can cause baldness
Sometimes the baldness goes to who deserves it. I guess like that's what it's that way
But if I bald you see brain, this is my hairline since I was like 15 years old. It gave my hair
You're not even bald. Well, I you would think by these images made of me that I am like I have actually I have a mullet
But then I'm bald. I mean that's the picture. That's the image of me
I mean, I've had this I've always said these are where my horns go my dad actually had these and so I'm proud of them
You're not all chill like I think you know a thing that is and J dog. They were cursed so
Yeah, they're balls. Oh my god, J dog. I
Don't want to say it but J dog
Just say it. He's a simp. He's a simp. Oh
Big time bowing to Sam man
Sam ends like get on your knees bitch and he went like this and he put his head down like that
To Sam and you're gonna let some poor weekend with Down syndrome boss you around like that
Respect is gone. I mean fuck
Sam is a fucking fat fuck. He needs to go and my 600 pound like or something. He should I
Mean, I like any to visit from doctor now room gang is cute
I mean, it's like but if he turns into what salmon is a big fat ugly fuck
And we have his real pictures.
I mean, it's like, I mean, people know they seem,
they seem, they seem to say, I mean,
people just don't seem to care.
I guess cause they're not.
He looks like a, he looks like a batter version
of Bozo the clown.
Yeah. He looks like, he looks like,
he looks like homie the clown, you know,
on my 600 pound life.
He looks like Eddie Murphy in the, in the crump
and meet the clumps as, as Bozo the clown.
I mean, it's like, it's just sad. It's scary.
Okay.
There's you meet the clumps. He's all those people at the table at once farting and stuff. I mean, that's him
Spell two words
Yard and shout out to the shout outs. He doesn't even spell them right and those aren't even real words
Talking about a cooking Papa's or something like what the fuck I mean
I think it means I'm making French fries or something because Papa's mean potatoes and Spanish does that well
I mean he is hungry all the time
So I mean he's but he's sitting in like a fucking a little like beach chair at a folding picking table with an empty
fish tank behind him
judging everyone else
Hungry hungry hippo ass
Have you seen this picture?
Yeah, he's ugly as fuck
I don't have to say it. I mean, it's like everyone knows, but you know, no, no
You know what the saddest part is is like he's like, you know, I guess he's he his show started as like
I'm gonna open a deck of you to your cards and that's what it started out as okay
Do your little you Joe show and somehow like, you know, he got my beat or something like that
He just had to get into the drama then he farms the drama
He uses her to do it. She's so dumb as fuck. She's even know
Oh, you could smell the insecurity on him. I was here as well. The problem with these people they're so fucking
They have no self-confidence
Right the derral just said it. He hates the way he looks like why he won't come up. He has no confidence
Oh, and then this fucking omate, this fucking douchebag omate.
Well, I understand why bitch is not coming up, because she's a lady.
Oh, ladies are stalked, but Sandman, you should come up, bitch.
And it's like, I'm not gonna come up.
Oh, what are you gonna say?
I mean, it's like, am I listening to some Looney Tunes card?
I mean, it's like the most ridiculous fucking shit I've ever heard in my life.
Rain, I can't even take this anymore.
How do I know these people even?
I mean, this, give me out of here.
rain you can you just don't give him attention
Just starve him of the of the attention. They crave so much. I just got a I just got a light bulb
I will never mention those motherfuckers ever again, and we're just gonna move on
Who's that burning joint?
Burning joint Aubrey Plaza
I don't know. Is that like a place in New York?
Oh, that's he said Aubrey like that's essential girl's name, isn't it?
Aubrey, yeah, I thought it was like Audrey,
like a little shop of course.
Oh, I remember seeing that movie one time with JT.
You did?
Yeah.
You say you wanted to.
I forgot the plot of it though.
Wasn't it something about plants or something?
Yes.
Okay, the plot of it is, there's an energy guy.
His name is Rick Moranis, I heard of Rick Moranis.
No.
You ever seen a honey eye?
You're the main guy in the movie?
Yeah, honey eye shrunk with the kids.
You ever seen that movie?
No, I've ever seen guys naming Rick Moranis movie. I'm in the chat Rick Moranis
I mean he was a big big big. I mean I can pull up his picture. He's very famous
Is he ugly? Oh?
By the way, I just want to show you something. Okay, so you know what? I mean someone did a show tonight and they were saying. Oh
my god
You know, there's two great streamers Brandon Q and beta. Okay. You know what this person said about that streamer who said that to him yesterday
Let me see if it's even still in the play. Oh, here it is here
I'll show you the picture that he put up of this person. Okay for her to be glazing. I'm sure yeah
I know I just said hi. Oh ghostbusters using ghostbusters to look at this post he made on her and she says he's
And he also had me because apparently I said, you know
I set her up, but then she's friends with him and she fucking treats me like shit
But let's just look here's a picture that he posted of her yesterday. Okay. I didn't post this
I'm gonna share to show her so I guess she hasn't seen it. I will show you
You want to see the picture he posted Brandon Q
Her her she was just a brilliant streamer. She loves the streams. Here's what he posted of her. Do you see it?
Is it on the screen yet? Yes, okay
Oh, announcement. As of today, I'll be cutting out contact, exposing Gamble and other people.
My main focus will be exposing the fugitive of the law, the dirty-ass AIDS monkey, and having her face justice and exposure to the public.
But we're imposing her!
Who's that supposed to be?
Guess.
Alex?
Yes.
So what? That does look like her.
rain. Come on. I don't want to go to his level. I don't want to see his level. Okay, come on. I mean, I think that's cruel, but no, but it's like-
Well, she is bald.
Okay, well, let's get over that. Okay, but okay, there she is in front of his Mexican restaurant by his house, okay? I think she was soft.
Why is she in front of a Mexican restaurant if she's racist? She doesn't like Mexican restaurants.
No, she went to New Mexico to track him down. I guess he lives in that little shack behind that place right there. Okay, but look, let's see what else he posted.
Well, she doesn't even like Mexicans.
She calls them Latinos, but look at that. That's a heater. It looks good
Oh my gosh, you have to be more specific than that because we're not just Latinos or Mexicans
Okay, so here's the other thing imagine platforming an AIDS monkey
Fyald Pornstar Niglet that defiled your dead dad
and tried to set damage to your family's business
and financial interests at Cult of Psyche.
Good, now let's, everyone boycott your ass again
and let it be known, Alex Cock-Eyed Aids Niglet.
This is what he says about her.
And cat choking Aids boy, Meth Head Psyche,
rejected by me, thrown to the curb.
Okay, surprise.
This is what he's saying about you, Alex.
You're glazing on your show tonight, okay?
Little bit weird. Did I ever say anything like that to you?
But I mean what have I would I ever know?
But go glaze him and mad at me because I introduced you and you said he's great tonight. Oh
He's so smart. Isn't he Alex do you agree with what he says?
He says we both have AIDS. I mean geez you hate you came with RG and say oh, I mean he's crazy
Have you been dipping into the chocolate?
Thank you. Are you having the cacao? Have you been dipping into the chocolate? What like what kind of chocolate will you wonka?
What are you talking about?
Never mind
You don't my cock
Cacao no
Are you gonna? You're gonna look cool
Forget it. I don't know La Llorona
Like your owner. What does she have to do with it?
everything
Bruh, Bruh
Yeah, yeah, you're I see that look in your eye. It's not towards you sweetheart
Okay, nothing rain rain go away. Okay. I'm not saying that. Okay
I'm saying
Why are you saying that I dip in the chocolate? What kind of chocolate buddy? What's what's the joke?
Is there a joke behind it? What oh did I fuck a black person? Yes, I have but it was like
It was the he fucked me actually and was many years ago. Is that why you're so attached to this witch?
No, that's because of the probably the voodoo and the the the moon rituals and the
Gaslighting put a curse on you. Oh, yeah. Oh more than that
Do you know I supposed to turn into a a werewolf a lobo?
At on the full moon and then when I didn't and I was clean shaven and well groomed
She said I turned into a woman
The fuck is right easy shit. You need to rebuke that shit. I have oh my god. I
Have giant pupils on a meth really my people large rain
No, they look normal. Oh, holy level in go fuck yourself. You're on
Rain just verify. I don't have big big pupils. Thank you. I don't FG. I
Well, what what shit? I mean, it's like I don't know. I know I know some of it. I've seen it
You know, there's something called dreams and I do have a talent in dreams sometimes where I can like actually go
Can you after a project?
Mm-hmm. Oh shit
But there's there's something called, you know, there's people like also it's like, you know
I can see when people are fucking with the dreams and stuff like that
It's kind of like the man behind the curtain and then toto comes and pulls down the curtain and there's fucking wicked witch sitting there
Sucking the Wizard of Oz is dick. Oh, it's all block. It's all
Well, yeah, that's what happened. I mean, it's like jeez. I've never been able to ask Joe for joy
It's not as I
Can I can talk to you privately and I can give you some I know it's just y'all some people develop
Yeah, some people are more natural than others, but it's like it's also not as hard like people put a lot of like
Oh, you're supposed it's like, you know, I think it's like an out-of-body experience more when it's actually more like imagine
but
If you can like visualize and you close your eyes if you can visualize you're pretty much there the astral realm is the imagination
and so
I'll leave it at that
More subconscious that's what I was gonna say the subconscious like in the astral state is kind of like the subconscious is
Ruling it rather than the conscious mind and so
Subconscious but still stay conscious enough to witness it then you can pretty much
That's pretty much it
Yep, me know she is
Nancy, let's say she was she was because that's all over, you know, I
Don't know if she started talking talking into big fat
Shrek Kate about my cats and stuff like that to fucking piss me off
But you know that will but she's already talked about it. Just still talking about your cats. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah
Leave the cats out of this. They're innocent like my kids and it's like nobody else's fuck fucks with any
I mean, I mean, it's like except fucking sickos like some of these people fuck with peoples
You know talk about people's kids and all this listen. It's like it's like and then it's like someone came in
Oh, well, we heard two of your cats have been eaten by you or something like that. I'm like the fuck
I mean, it's like and then it's like oh, she's sitting on Kate's tonight. Okay
Just reveal yourself more and more. I mean, it's like you're already revealed if she practically
She's more naked than she was on the tennis court in that porno film. Okay
Grossly get tennis racket up your butt and leave me the fuck alone bitch
Not you're right. Not you're right. I'm sorry. I know that's crazy FG
Yeah, well near death experience in the hospital bed. It's like
DMT is released
during I think Comento states and
That kind of thing and so yes, I think and then the DMT will really help with that too. You try very yeah
I know that near death, you know people that I have known that have gone to the death process, you know
Do experience these hallucinations or we call them hallucinations. They could just be seeing through the veil at that point
Okay, or don't they call it like?
You know like a reel of your whole life like your flat your life flashes before your eyes second
Yeah, but that's what happened. That's what life is
Your your life is life flashing before your eyes and if you think about your whole life
It's like to God your life is like a little like a week like a little diamond a wink
It's like a little like
like rubbing out like an eyelash like that.
That's what one life is to like God.
It's like a whole life, like a lifetime
because there's billions and billions, you know?
Time to repent.
Go ahead and look at my community wall.
I have repented on there tonight.
I'm way ahead of you.
We're all just dust in the wind.
To what?
I thought you said a wiener.
No, that's what you wanted.
Dang it, Ray.
Oh, and it flashes, yeah.
Oh, and it flashes, time to repan.
Hey, Ray, this is one of your favorite snacks.
Look at this.
Oh, a hot Cheeto.
Cheeto puffs, flaming hot Cheeto puffs.
I never get the puffed ones.
I usually get the, you know, the lime, the lemon.
I have a lime soup.
Oh, you got a match of
Hey, so Darryl's or FG says he almost had enough fire his life didn't flash before his eyes
He was choking on smoke and then felt like going to sleep and you slept
So what happened like you got rescued or you inhale smoke from being interested to hear a little bit more about that
It's really interesting FG. I've known FG since up before I started doing my show
I met him on another terror channel and he's a
So so cool to see people that I
Have known on YouTube before I was on YouTube, you know, it's like I when I started on YouTube
Like really about watching it. I didn't talk on YouTube for maybe two years
I even talk in a chat for probably two years
Then I slowly start I was because I was paranoid. I started to talk talking in chats
Then I said that I got started becoming a mod
Eventually stay dressed. Will you stay blessed by John?
Don't tell me what to do though. I don't like being told what to do. I will stay dressed, but I might be in the speedo
If I drink too fast so fireman stopped stepped on you picked your ass up
You woke up three two weeks later in the hospital. Wow. See your comatose. It's crazy
me
So look what else I have to eat tonight. I can't see it. What is it? Oh devour white cheddar?
Never had those bacon has bacon in it. It's like it's like basically like
upper-class version of a stover's down
So I'm gonna put this in my convection oven right now.
Beautiful, huh?
Okay, right there.
Part of me, Ray.
Sure.
I have a reading for you, if you'd like.
Yes.
Okay.
Well, I'm gonna-
Remember, I'm a Libra.
Okay, you're a Libra.
Okay, well, I'll use these.
These are kind of Oracle cards.
I'll use these three.
These are like, let me turn off my background.
I have the Fairy Deck, the Secret Garden Deck,
and like a Mermaid Deck.
And I see that the moon is full tonight.
So.
Yes, the moon is very, very in its majesty tonight.
So we're gonna go to the fairy dust first.
Okay.
And so I'll pull three from each.
So you're gonna get a nine card reading, okay?
But these are for short little messages,
but they might, oh, this one popped out first.
This one says friends.
Okay.
And it says, all the love, your light extends its reflection shown in chosen friends.
And friends are the family you choose in a certain way, but also it's your true friends.
They will your true friends will reveal themselves your enemies will reveal themselves
But you know, I'm thankful for my true friends. So I do have some good true friends
I am too and it resonates with me too because today, you know, like I was talking a couple of friends and you know
Like I'm just grateful to have them. Yeah
This one says lead the way. You're a leader of some like there's something you can show the way to people
Should the people somehow this one says
Take the reins today rain. It says take the reins
okay nice others will follow if you leave the way so you can be quite a good influencer i would say
i don't know if you have a show or something you might want to do on to me because i think you
could be a leader in something you know i used i used to have a stream but i just stopped doing
it because people are so toxic yeah i would say maybe you know it may be a good idea not to you
know but oh this one says music okay so is music really special to you important to you yes i love
where the music plays, joy will follow.
Okay?
Awesome.
So there's something.
Music is my life.
Good.
Beautiful.
Maybe there's some kind of like,
I don't know, leader of some kind of band
or something like that.
I don't know if you like,
if you play an instrument or if like,
or just like you can like.
No, but my dad does.
Okay, your dad does.
Well, maybe there's some talents in there
that's untapped, you know?
I don't know.
He's very talented.
Yeah, well, you know,
you're your father's daughter.
And so your talent is here.
Don't forget that.
Okay?
Oh, thanks, Mikey.
Well, look, it's true.
It is true.
You have also relax.
This is for the next day.
Relax.
And it says delight in powdered gold sunshine.
OK.
So maybe it's the time to, like, go to the beach to lay in the sun,
to soak up some rays and that kind of thing.
And if there's anything that's been.
stressing you out, or, you know, it's just a time to get away from those fears.
And the next one is, oh, strength, oh, you got the strength ring, okay?
So you got a lot of strength right there.
And it says, don't let weeds and thistles cultivate in your garden.
Yeah, yeah, so we have a garden, like, I love the idea that the mind is a garden.
And it's like, old thoughts, it's like having a beautiful garden.
Bad things are horrible thoughts you have a bunch of vines and weeds and it's overgrown and you know
And and there's you know poison ivy and they're poisonous stuff and all kind of you know, so I cultivate and
You know, basically put the negative things out and that pulled two or three from this one yet
Do you remember? You know, you know what JT told me? He said, um, don't wrestle with pigs because you know
You'll break it dirty. Yeah, I love it. And the pig will like it. Yes
That's what they said about gay sex to me
Fortunately, it was true. I'm just kidding. Okay. I'm so sorry
Okay, I have one more secret garden
Let's go to the secret garden. You ever see the secret garden here. Let me hear a secret garden
No
Secret garden is actually it was I read it. It's a really good book. It's about I forgot what exactly it's about
But I know that the girl gets a key and then she finds a secret garden
She goes to the garden and she can read and be alone in there and then it's magical somehow
I forgot exactly what it's about. This one says move a rolling stone gathers
No moss, okay
So it's not saying move away from where you are, but it's saying
Get up and dance or you know, you know, I feel us. That's what we say in Spanish. Yeah
Your batteries on
Hey, look at this one
potential
The littlest key can open the heaviest door. Okay. Oh
Yeah, it's like if you have if you have even like this it's like a little it's just like the littlest
the littlest speck of of
Pure white light can light up the darkest universe, right?
It's like just a little light think about all the darkness that's the spells from that, right?
It's like because the dark
That let the light overtakes the darkness. It's not it's not really the other way around
Usually, okay. I'm one more one more. So one more for rain come through
This one says be presence. Okay, and it says
Use the hours don't count them
And so it's like, yeah, it's like, don't be concerned about what the, yeah, the time that's passing, but can be concerned about what you're doing with us.
Yeah, you're concerned about time. Like, you don't think about anything else. Hi, Kitty. Is that Lola?
It's Lola.
Hi, Lola. Oh, she's so cute.
My traps they don't they don't even lay on my lap like they they just want to get up and move everywhere else
Then again, they're so young like they'll they'll almost be two years old
Well as a few years old
So um FG was says that you know Darryl and FG been talking in chat and about you know
The spirit finding the body and then FG is like you could say that that the universe didn't want him to go yet
No, and it's like I love that kind of thing too because people that have had near-death experiences a lot of times they'll say
They'll see somebody that they love and the person will be like it's not your time go back
But you have to do it right now, right? I'm just and you just said it's moving me to chill
I just watched it. See I watched a movie. It was a kind of trashy movie last night
But it's like and then it may be taken by as a trashy move by some right? It's called 68 kill
And it's kind of got violence and sex and all this kind of stuff
But there are these little gems in the movie.
Like a few, not too many.
Is it like a Gore-Fetish film?
No, it's kind of about this guy
and he has this crazy ass girlfriend, right?
She's like, she's hot and he's kind of like,
he's not an nerdy guy, but he's, you know,
she likes to do, she likes to slap him around
when they're having sex and stuff like that.
And she's real crazy, right?
And he's like, well, I love crazy.
And then she's like, well, she's, but she's a prostitute too.
And she's like, well, hey, I was with my John, whatever.
And he, I saw him put like 70 grand in the safe
and she watched and put the, you know,
put the combination of the safe.
She's like, let's go rob him for that money or whatever.
And so she gets her boyfriend involved in the,
in the, in that kind of stuff.
And it gets crazier and crazier.
You have a whole new look at life now, believe it.
That's awesome.
And that's, that's, like getting in the perspective
and that's a, that is a blessing, right?
And it's a blessing, and you are meant to be here.
And that means there's work for you to do,
and there's something for you to still do here,
like many things, you know?
So bless you, and he's a really good guy.
So this is Daryl.
I mean, everyone here is good.
I don't care if I have 10 people here.
It's like, I do have, I just noticed it's like,
I lost so many horrible people from my show.
And so people will say, oh, his show's dead or whatever.
But the people that really have stayed are like the most awesome people and now I get to pay more attention to them
I don't get so distracted by these fucking assholes and I mean there's just like I mean there's there's really true evil in the
World and it's like I finally seen it. Yeah, I would always like say oh, there's good in everybody and everything
That's not necessarily true anymore
You know, it's like some people are empty vessels take purely run by demons and
Want to be nasty, right? You know, it's like, oh, I'm here to kill steal and destroy
Just like it says in the Bible. There's some there's some people like that and you got to watch out for them
They also have even wicked tongues usually they'll be like
That or they'll be going or they wink their eyes like that, you know
Because he's an angel. He is an angel
Darrell you talk out here would need it. Yes. I mean it's he I know Darrell Darrell you see what's going on
It's like, you know when I need like today. I had basically I had Brandon Q putting bots in the chat saying I
Rejected you he's so I mean why does he care so much like who rejected?
I mean, of course I rejected him a long time ago because if I didn't then why is he still trying to come on my show?
I am I going to his show or anything? No, so obviously I
Banned him for my show
He keeps trying to come on
Yet he rejected me if he rejected me wouldn't that mean he wouldn't be
Involved anymore little gems Joni just little gems little little you know what just like that little tiny little
Like the tiniest key opens
The biggest door right?
Dead by daylight
I like I totally I totally forgot the other two form bomb you like not so long ago
Like is because that big fat that monster Kate told them to and then you know you know what this guy
I'm tripping sip
She told him to come in and we're bombing and he did it twice in a row
And then he asked to come back again on the panel so he wouldn't do it again
And I was like no, I'm like fool me fool me once shame on you fool me twice shame on me, you know and then
Kate piped up. Oh, he was going to tell you some great gossip. Do I look like, you know, Mike Walker from National Enquirer? I'm not a gossip. I don't care about big fucking gossip around this stupid panel or shit. I care about, you know, growth, cool things, like, you know, helping, like, good, good. I mean, it's like, if we have to get to some shit first, I mean, we have to, but look at this, look at what I have right here. Wait, I do have a beautiful frosted glass right here. Let me just.
Oh, did you put that in the freezer?
I did. And then I'm gonna...
It's a nice frost.
There we go. Cheers, guys.
It's a celebration, okay?
Cheers.
Hi, Lola.
Lola wants some champagne.
Oh, she wants attention.
Lola wants attention.
It's okay. Come sit in my lap, sweetheart.
You can see she's right here. Look.
Aww.
She's so comfortable.
She is. She is.
So, cheers, guys. Cheers, okay?
Hey, no, here's a here's a here's a toast. Hey, here's a toast
Champagne to real friends real pain for fake friends about that true friends true hearts
You love her as she does. Oh the FG when I first got her
When I first got her I had a few cats and the guy broader incident
I found this cat on this like walking on the side of the freeway basically right or the highway and
I was like I was like I was like don't I was like don't leave her here. I was like
Because if I see the cat, I'll fall in love, and I have enough cats right now.
And he said, okay, can I leave her here for 10 minutes, I'll be right back?
I'm like, okay.
And he left her here in like a little carrier, they brought her in.
And I was sitting on the couch, trying to not pay attention.
And I heard like she meowed once or something like that.
And I looked, I had to open the thing.
And then she came out and she had her eyes were just covered in boogers and stuff.
You know, eye boogers, right?
Yeah, and I have this comb. It's like a it's like a comrade like that and I combed out her eyes and
Then she opened her eyes. I don't think you can see her eyes, but she has the most beautiful green eyes
Close them a little bit, but now is that I don't love and you know and she's here
Yeah, yeah
Thank you. That's be yours. She adopted you in order to I mean all my cat and you know and all my and like sometimes, you know
Sometimes you're sometimes somebody else that doesn't have a pet
Is a need of one and then it's like and then they go I just believe it
You know, there's there's things that happen, you know, the with you know
Feral cats and stuff like that and that kind of thing, but that's not in this city in this city like every but all the pets are swept up
There's no there's no shelter even right because there's no need
There's no feral cat colonies all the animals are assimilated into the neighbor
So I believe that there's some people that were maybe lonely and the cat has been to to go to them and and they and they and I
raised them, you know, I just like
like people say oh my god he had nine cats and now he has like you know three cats or whatever right
okay but i had nine cats because i had four cats at that time and then one of them gave birth and
so that i had nine am i supposed to if i had nine cats do you think they wouldn't be talking
It would say, what do you have so many cats?
I mean, it's like, okay, I raised them.
They're just like, Lola raised them.
And Lola was a really good mom.
But when the cat was able to eat on his own
and didn't have to suck on her tittie, right, for milk,
she didn't want them sucking on her tittie
when they were big and they could eat on their own.
So she would swat him away.
And so, I'm sorry, FG, you buried him in your backyard.
Yeah, I do have a I have a couple like you know kittens buried because
You know I had another cat named Remy and she had two litters and there were a couple that didn't make it
You know
And so I do have like a little pet cemetery too, but you know what I mean those are angels too. I mean
You know, it sucks for the kittens that don't get a chance because you know, they're I do believe
They hopefully they come back into their form. So who so someone's saying hey Kate. So Kate
I've messed up Kate blocks. I don't see Kate in the room. It's our cake in the room. I don't see Kate
It's Kate in the room. Does anybody see Kate? I don't see her
Boston Bridges here. I don't see Boston Bridges either. I've been blocked or am I crazy?
Um, Nick, I think you're in the wrong chat because Kate is Kate and Boston vision are not here
Must be type you must be watching two shows at once and you're confused
Boston yeah, I don't I don't see those people
Bridget has never been to my chat. I don't think she likes me very much
Even though I was fairly pleasant to her
I mean, I was like, oh, you're not as horrible as I thought you were you know when I talked to her
But then she talked a lot of shit and so I don't really care for her anymore. That's for Kate
I was, you know, Kate, I would let her on my show, say whatever she wanted, hang out.
I was totally kind, nice to her.
She didn't like Brandon, and when I just met him, I mean, of course she was right that
he was a total piece of shit, right?
But at the time, everyone was like, a bunch of trolls were like...
get him out of here, get him out.
And I was like, well, he can be in the chat.
And turned into this whole thing,
but she was the first person
to start this predator protectors thing.
She started this boycott of my show.
She started posting me, I've used my cats.
She did all this shit.
And still, I still apologize for her
because I did make a video
where I turned her into Shrek's sister.
Okay, it's called Big Bet Kate.
It's a great video I'll try to look for later.
But anyway, he had the legend of Big Bet Kate.
But anyway, I ended up apologizing to her.
She told me to, she told me to shove it up my ass or something like that.
I even apologized to her one more time and I made a nice, I took her picture where she's like,
you know, looks like a ogre and I made it into like a nice like little stylized cartoon where she
didn't look so god-awfully disgusting and gross and ogreous, right? I made it look cool.
And she told me to shove that up my ass too. And so then I showed her actual picture and she
Yeah, like I wish my cat sat on my lap. Oh
She you know she does she goes under the covers and she cuddles with me and she starts purring under the cover
So she's the sweetest cat. Oh
She purrs
My cats never sit still for anything
Well, Lola is a special special cat, you know and
I'm lucky to have Lola, you know
Despite, you know, how much she really loves you. Yeah, Lenore loves me too, but Lenore's a little bit a little bit hot right now
so Lenore likes to spend time outside and
But Lenore comes in I mean, oh, she's in heat
No, she's not he it's just hot outside or hot inside and outside it's summertime
You know and it's like and she got she's black and so you know
I guess it's like no maybe absorbs into the firm more
And she just likes to be outside in the summertime and lay lay in the sun and stuff even at night
I think about 80 degrees right now
But Lola is I have this a fan on Lola
Well, let's chill you see this book. I have I got a new book. Here's to the book
Things I can't say
During a video call. Why?
So that probably get my channel taken down
Okay, your cat purrs. Oh, there's Nancy. We were graced like yes. Oh, yes. I know. Thank you, Joni. I mean, it's like
Yeah, I'm gonna be more private. I'm like, you know, I
It's like, you know, the thing is like, you know, we need a beautiful family when you have beautiful animals and it's like you think oh
I want to share and I'm so proud and I love and I want other people to see and appreciate and then it's like
We don't think about there's people that are just jealous and hateful
Yeah, you can't share everything because people are jealous and envious
Yeah, and then they think there's something called the evil eye and the evil eye is actually based on envy and jealousy
I mean that's that's what that I mean the evil eyes like literally like
Malikio or Malacca
It's like it's just jealousy and it's like they pray for your downfall
Yeah, but it's like and sometimes it's unconscious. They don't even know they're because sometimes people don't know about like, you know
The power of thought and magical spells and stuff like that and so but they're just jealous and that's the evil eye too
And so it's a lot of times it's unconscious that people do it
but
The thing is it's like anything people are jealous of like why can't they do it themselves
if they're I mean it's like we can we have the opportunity to
Because a lot of the times they're way too insecure and you know like they're unhappy with their own lives
Yeah, exactly, right. You're really wise actually. How do you get so wise?
Well, I don't know. You don't know. Hey, so what's got with are you mad? Are you in gaudy at odds right now because?
Why is he saying? He's saying JT is a Korean with Down syndrome and stuff
I was like, what's this about and then he's talking about somebody like he's like he's like, oh, you're so I don't know if he's
I always think he's talking about me, but he's like, oh you you know, he's talking about somebody like oh you stupid
Psychic empath and you think you're so I'm like he's talking about me or somebody
I don't know because he's always nice to me when he's on the panel and stuff
I need to ask about it. He read these nasty messages plus he said he was he was a tourist
He said he was a tourist, but he always told me he was a Gemini
Was he a liar too? Yeah. Well, that's the thing. Um, with him, like, I don't know, we kind of fell
out with him because, um, he got with somebody and it wasn't because we were jealous of their
relationship. We actually praised, praised the relationship, but, um, oh, with the pink hair.
Yeah. Like he got with her and then, um, so we were at her stream.
And God, he wanted me to ban Vader and I told him like I don't want to I don't want to ban Vader
He's he wasn't a mod there and she wasn't a mod why can't they do it?
No, they were mods, but God, he was demanding me to ban Vader. Why didn't he do it?
Because he wanted me to do it
Why is that?
Don't know like all of a sudden he was just like oh rain ban Vader and I'm like no I'm not gonna do that
That's some kind of like controlling motherfuckers. I mean it's like why he doesn't want to do it himself, right?
He wants what he wants Vader to be mad at you
He's the one blood on his hands gaudy. Come on gaudy
yeah, and
JT like he gets along with Vader and
You know like I had like I had like oh
a past beef with Vader, but like we smooth things out.
So we're on good terms with Vader.
And I told him, I don't want to do that.
And then he got mad at me, he started,
I don't know, like telling me things and like,
so yeah, like, it's just other people involved in,
you know, like it's just turning.
I mean, first of all, was it his chat
or his girlfriend's chat?
His girlfriend's chat. Okay, and so he was a mod there obviously
Yeah, so he's a mod
But he's trying to delegate somebody else to kick somebody out of the chat
So he's a mod trying to boss other mods around
Yeah, gotty. Gotty. That's really lame as fuck and it's like, you know, I don't know to us like it just like it was like a
180, you know, like and I know look at this rain. Look at that
nice
The as a Mexican does this kind of make your heartbeat a little fast? Yes, it does
You know in you know, you know in Chile they Chile, you know the country Chile, right? Mm-hmm
They don't like spicy food, but in Mexico they do
Yeah
Isn't that kind of strange?
Not really. I don't like spicy food in Chile. I mean it's named after our spicy pepper
Well, I don't know. I don't know the foods in Chile, like, really.
No, they don't like spicy food. They don't. They don't like spicy.
It's all, it's kind of, it's kind of more like bland there.
But Mexico, they love spicy. They love the jalapeno in Mexico.
I don't, life is funny though.
It's named Chile.
If I lived in a place called Spicy Pepper,
I'd probably like Spicy Pepper as I would think,
but I wouldn't think a place called...
What does Mexico mean in like another language? I don't know max. Oh, it comes from the old term
Don't say it again
Then I think one
Which is like a it's a now at
From the now at language, which is indigenous. Hmm. Have you ever seen?
What's the Mel Gibson movie?
Was I called, you know, we're talking about and the Hispanic
I guess I got the Mayans and the Assay.
What's that make?
Oh.
Apocalypto?
Apocalypto.
Have you seen that?
Yep.
How'd you like that movie?
I like that movie.
It's a good movie.
It was.
Have you ever seen the Passion of the Christ?
No, but I heard it was like really,
I don't know, it made a lot of people emotional.
Even people that aren't into the Christian faith.
I don't know.
I'm going to show you a scene from The Passion of the Christ.
I want to get your opinion.
No, I don't want to.
It's not bad.
It's not like, it's not bad.
It's like an interesting, it's my favorite scene.
It's only 20 seconds.
Okay.
I'm going to show you.
It's better to be 20 seconds.
It will be 20 seconds.
And poor for boring.
Okay.
Poor for boring.
I was going to play this quick, quick scene.
Okay, yeah, like basically like God he doesn't like us anymore
And so he just starts talking shit about us everywhere else like you know, I guess to get a reaction from us
But we don't get we don't give him a
Reaction, you know
No, I know is JT have Korean
No, they just like to make that shit up like oh, he's my he's my brother. He's my half-brother
He's qualified and all that
He's not your he's not your your half Korean brother with Down syndrome
No
I'm really
What is it? What if so he was just probably like probably sneeze when they took a picture of him and his eyes
Yeah, you know how they like to like screenshot like
I know yeah, I know I get told oh look at this second before and after the before picture is like me like when I would just
Had just like you know taking a shower. I was gonna go out to Mother's Day
I had my shirt on and I'm like you know have a short haircut
That picture is me after I woke up in the three in the morning, you know, half drunk with my you know
With my eyes, you know halfway closed and I was eating like a sandwich and
Anything look at psyche before and after like that was probably the next day
I mean, you know how different we can look from when I'm a shapeshifter fuck for fuck's sake
You know how different I can look but that's such a meme looks like he's let himself go. You know fucking good
I look tonight
Yeah, my motherfuckers listen listen listen my motherfuckers is they have I've lost and
Do you see wrinkles on my skin? Do you see a gray hair in my in my head? Do you see a bald spot on my
motherfuckers? Go fucking fuck yourself. These people that say this a bunch of fucking
They're like mongoloids. I mean, I mean really and they don't even show themselves on camera is the worst part. They're fucking
They're disgusting. I mean the ugliest people
are trying to point out
Nice looking people and said that they're ugly. Well, they're not showing themselves because oh my god
If they ever showed themselves, well, they'll be all over for them
But thankfully there's something called camera slips and that's why I like to collect camera slips
So if I ever show pictures camera slips
Hey, you should have kept the lens cap on your camera motherfucker, okay?
I mean, it's like, you know if you want to make fun of me and say and say all this shit about me
I will show you fuckers look like okay?
Not to scare anybody, okay, cuz I won't do it unless it's fucking someone like fucking BigBatKate, Sandman, Bita
I mean, I mean these fucking
Insignificant disgusting pieces of shit that shouldn't even exist if I had me say it to myself
Okay, okay. I'm gonna show myself for privacy reasons
Great. I've seen your picture and you're you're lovely, you know, you have glasses, you know
You're kind of like you're kind of like you me. I'm ugly and I'm a monkey
The hot librarian you're like a hot librarian kind of energy
Yeah, I don't know according to you me. I'm ugly and I look like a man. You mean it looks like a man
You mean it looks like a transgender, you know a Down syndrome Korea. She's a real down syndrome Korean fucking
Okay, I know but
I'm a flying monkey. I'm so sorry. I'm over back. I'll be right back. Can you go to the chat for a second?
Sure. I'll be right back
Hurry. Oh
Shit
What's up?
Everybody I'm not much of an entertainer psyche
I'm apparently old. Oh, who said that? You're beautiful on inside and outside.
We have a Zephyr in the chat. So Zephyr is like the West wind. Hey, thing that is, how are you?
Thing that, I have a question for thing that is though. Thing that is, hey, I didn't see
thing that is today and he was directing people towards some kind of poll and he kept saying,
oh, vote for psyche because that's the troll thing to do. Thing that I didn't know you were such a
Well, he is bald, psyche.
I thought he was Mr. Clean with, you know, AIDS.
I'm just kidding, not AIDS, I'm so sorry.
Hold on, Mr. Clean with the anorexia, okay, I'm sorry.
No, no, no.
Mr. Clean, Mr. Clean, if you survived the death camp.
Mr. Clean on a diet, okay, okay, I'm just kidding.
I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding.
I'm just saying what people say about me, okay, you know.
But I think there's an expert in trolling, though.
It's like, yeah, I told you I told you not to trust bald people because they do this type of shit all the time
But what is it the hair that makes people good? I don't understand. I'm
They're jealous. We have hair
It's a I want to I wonder if he has a hairy chest. Give a hairy chest. Okay. He's laughing. Okay
That's okay. See that here's what I like about thing that is as soon as it goes. I like his I like I like this
I see he can laugh at himself
That's like 90% of the journey, right?
My kitty looks like your kitty.
Thank you.
There's Lola right there.
That's like most of the journey
is being able to laugh at yourself.
And I know I take myself too seriously sometimes,
but I can laugh at myself most of the time.
But you have to understand,
really hurtful things have been said.
And sometimes I will, you know,
kind of react in a negative way.
But the thing that is, at least you can like,
if you can laugh right there,
You're not such a bad dude and in that and you can tease beta and you can tease that. Okay. You're not a bad dude, okay?
Long and lanky are you talking about me or the kitty cat?
sorry
mean that it thing that is I also appreciate the thing that is because
You've been with me for a while and you do have some kind of loyalty. Okay. Yeah, you got the sun
He's wearing sunglasses at night rain. You like that? No, I think he just wants a panel to sit on some times
Well, you know what so what you know? I saw this clip today. It's on this channel called salmon and friends
And he's like, Bita, I'm concerned.
You know, oh, you have some guy bringing a dog to your house
and he was so concerned about her.
Fuck you.
Fuck you, you little ass.
Don't be worried about me.
He's like, Bita, I'm just trying to get a bet, bet.
I mean, she's a hateful monster.
I mean, it's like, do you remember the thing that is?
It was sad.
It's on Samman and Friends channel.
Everyone hates your cat's name.
My cat's name is Lola.
What's your cat's name, Kid A?
I like it from South Park.
It's like Hartman's cat's name, Kid A.
Thing that is, yeah.
I'll show the clip, hold on.
I'm gonna play a clip right in real quick.
Let me take it, I'm gonna bring it up.
Yeah, there's this famous YouTube streamer gamer named Keso
and his cat's name is Kitty.
Oh
My kid so so yeah, so so Sam thing that is you're famous
Nothing this because you've actually made this channel called salmon and friends and I just want you to see cuz maybe maybe we're drunk at the time
Or something, but I want to only see a beat it talks to you when you were like
Beta, are you okay? Here's all he said all he said was
Worried about your safety and so that's all he said listen to how this witch
Talks to him. I just want everyone to see it's gonna be revealed. Okay. I'm gonna reveal everything. Okay. I'm not afraid
I'm not afraid to show the truth. Okay. I think that is you forgot is what happened. Okay. You see on the screen. Yep
Okay, here we go
Well, I mean, you know, we were concerned, you know, what are you worried about I was worried about your safety, okay?
Well my safety is a lot worse on the internet people in real life are fucking cool as fuck
I know but that wasn't real life real life beta. That's what I mean. I was concerned for your safety
I cooked three eggs or four
But he said I didn't even need to cook that but he liked it and he ate all of it
Good, I'm glad everything's
Fine that's good. Well, I mean what the fuck are you worried about?
Or you worried when people were sending comments to me?
No.
Yes, like, how can you?
No, you weren't.
At least the stranger told me.
I explained to him, I was like, this happens to me.
And he was just like, these people are saying this
and this and that.
And I was like, yeah, this is what happens to me.
And he's like, right around the corner,
you ever need help?
I'm here.
We don't, okay, I didn't know that and you're alone with the stranger, okay?
That's why I do everything on the panel.
Everything is cooking great.
He went down to the dog.
Look at my cat.
They're like, what is going on?
They smell the dog.
I don't want you to give a shit about my safety good nobody or it does again you're fucking cut
Okay, well, how about let's watch this you're with Sandman is that a play a clip of like, you know
My sister bringing cleaning supplies and being being sweet and stuff
Oh, look at this, look at this, look at this family.
What's up, y'all?
What's up, man?
God damn, I couldn't believe that shit.
Huh?
Summer was rubbing Tommy's back.
They was having a fucking therapy session.
And then they could be, she don't even know that,
then they could be lying in the therapy session.
Tommy James streamed himself, go to a therapy session,
bullshitting with the therapist.
Just like how he was bullshitting with summer and she was eating it up, and I'm like god damn summer
Only if you knew better man
Only if you knew that nigga recorded himself at the therapist
playing games with the therapist
crazy
You'll be though are you on a delay? Are you watching like the stream like ten minutes behind us some shit?
What's up with you, man?
Be the god to be watching the stream on some type of delay man
What happened oh it's in there some more
My fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my fault, my
That was my niggas, uh niggas say you were controlled with the same nigga. Uh, your table your table looked like controllers table
Bloggers table you got fucking chin hairs and
I keep turning. I've got a dining table. I've got two tables on the side. I keep turning my certain papers
I keep my print papers. I just don't move them like my mail is turning shit
Yeah, I don't like it. I don't move them. So I guess they need the tables. I'm like
That's my papers money. Don't move my papers. I want to know what's going on
I'm glad I didn't really say nothin' then.
I did it for the chat, man.
We're all listening to you, Sam, and you deserve that.
I've been told you I've got friends come our top friends over and they
Doing their friends given tomorrow
I'm hosting it. Yeah, I was literally on mute. Yes. I mean when they get start talking in the background. I get nosy
When they just get to talking in the background. I gets nosy
Huh?
That's the cat owner. My fact. That's the cat owner who he's talking. That's the cat owner right there
Fucking Spanish Prezi nigga get Prezi
But I heard someone say, I love you.
What?
Yeah, Chad.
Yeah.
A dude?
You heard a dude say, I love you?
Somebody in the chest said they was clipping it.
What's that nigga's name right there?
Ass eater, ass eater creature.
Say he clipped in everything, nigga.
They love and say love.
Why would I love you?
What a bunch of weirdos invested in dumb drama.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I like Ron.
I do like Ron.
Because Ron is real because Ron actually like Ron will go hard on like anybody that deserves it
but he
He knows I didn't serve it. So it wasn't that hard on me. We have another guest here. Oh, is that rain?
Hi, hey, sorry, I had to drop I didn't hear you
It's okay, I know you have that.
Hi Chanel, hi sweetheart.
Yeah, and so I remember Sam and my sister like came over
and like brought me like, you know,
they, I believe she's like some Clorox one time.
He's like, oh look, look, I'm doing this now.
Look at how I made it.
And there he is with his, like,
I'm sorry to make you move your face,
but yeah, there he is with his dad and his brother.
I mean, this guy, he's in a wife beater.
He's like a 300 pound Puerto Rican guy,
sweating, armpits, disgusting.
Just a bunch of fucking weirdos worried about drama, like.
And then he has the nerve to talk about my floor.
No one ever said vacuum my floor.
I mean, even if my floor was dirty, you know.
A bunch of weird guys invested in YouTube genre like it's my whole fucking life
It's just so hypocritical, but you know what you know, that's called right there
Karma karma
It's like are you gonna if like if he didn't call out everybody for everything
But I have a reason to have played that clip. No
He must smell like he was smelling sausage eggs and ass. Okay. They want to be mean girls so bad
I mean they must sit and watch like mean girls every fucking weekend and like, you know
Want to be that that girl that got hit by the bus at the end of the movie? I don't know. I mean, yeah
They want to be Regina George
So bad Virginia George's it's my bus. Do they remember that part of the movie or did they yeah pass out by that time because they're on so many
No, she did she did get hit by the bus did they're on they're on cough medicine and white claws and stuff like that
I mean, it's like it's okay
They're not gonna sit through the whole Mean Girls movie and find out Regina George actually gets hit by a bus
Which should happen to them, you know, these weirdos these weirdos are fighting to be the Queen D
Well, they're the Queen
There's a queen asshole. I mean, it's like you're an offendable. Oh, I'm an offendable too Zephyr. I like your name though
Zephyr you're like a wind you're like the West wind or something if I have a upset on stop sign
It says dots
You know upset on stop sign says dots
You know dogs. I'm eating a broke protein bar. I'm so sorry. I didn't mean to interrupt you
But you know what you know dots is it's like it sounds like do transsexuals
Is that, is that what Sam is?
It's a D-D-O-T-S, it was just transsexual
or do Taylor Swift, one of those two,
but I think Taylor Swift wouldn't be a transgender though.
It's a dot sign.
I'm eating a protein bar.
Are you protein?
Or are you anti?
I'm eating protein.
You're a lady?
Oh my God, I'm so sorry, sweetheart, I'm so sorry.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking to the person, Zephyr, in the chat.
I think it's a transgender person.
Oh, it is they said they're a lady's sorda. I don't I don't quite I don't understand
She's like a female like a female like like like Christine like what about Christine today?
I heard like Christine says something and oh, yeah, somebody came on beat is in there like
They're like, you know and scream that movie they're like
I want to see you in the, you know, open the phone.
Oh, my gosh, you sound exactly like...
I was like, oh, they're everyone's like, who is that?
And I was like, oh, it's Christine.
Do you like scary movies?
I'm not watching with Christine.
I don't know what she's going to do to me.
Probably slice my throat.
Hey, who wants to come up on the panel?
Okay, I'm here with a beautiful lady that she's taken.
Thank you.
She has taken don't forget that
Zephyr was a guy cuz that's a guy's name. Isn't it? Hey Zephyr is like a lady
But may have had a penis at one point. I'm not sure. I just don't know. Okay. Okay, never mind
So Zephyr is a woman. Okay. Zephyr is a woman. I'm so sorry. I thought you were just trolling me Zephyr
I was just rolling back Zephyr a voxel
What does that mean like avocado with the Zell
Hold on, I'm gonna just pick.
You know what, Zephyr does mean the West Wind.
Zephyr, do you know Cupid and Psyche?
No, no, okay.
Apparently they birthed two kids.
Zephyr has never had a penis except in her vagina.
Is that safe to say, because she had two kids?
I'm sorry, I'm being so gross.
I'm so sorry, I'm sorry.
Oh, my macaroni's ready.
Lola.
Okay, these are our 15 minutes.
Do you see Lola over there?
Yeah, you see Lola.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry
Confrontation hell. Who the hell is it? Oh hell no, you know if you want to oil Russell. It's bald
Motherfucker. Yeah
Good to talk to you too, right?
It is a troll. I didn't know he was I don't trust you
Okay
Oh, no, no, be nice. It didn't is because it isn't my friend. They'd be nice to me. I'm just saying I don't trust him
Well, yeah, I don't
Listen, I don't trust a Canadian with a tan either, but he was just in Mexico. I
Was hoping he might have gotten kidnapped by the cartel. Oh my god, rain hoping
Maybe next time maybe next time next time hopefully next time. I don't want to find thing
electrocuted in a pile of oil you know somewhere please just no if you'll be
chopped up more like it I need anything that is alive to be on my show okay so
why are they
Why rain just leave things alone. He's protected by me. Okay. He could be a live streaming with you when like, you know
Like your soul
I don't know how disloyal he is how much he talks about me to beat us how much he likes me to more than me
I like this guy. I just like him. He's not a bad person
He's not. He's not a good person.
I'm pretty good.
He's better. He's more good than bad.
I will say you're more good than bad.
I told you this Frankie.
Both people are evil.
They are.
Well I heard that from Mr. Clean
when he didn't clean my floor as well.
It's from the Bond movies man.
the ball. The villain. Kind of
Bruce Willis. Show. I didn't
say it was Bruce Willis. I
said Bond movies. You guys talk
for a second. I love you. You're
leaving me alone with her. Hurry
up. Hurry up. Psyche. I don't
want to be alone with this
bulb. Damn it. So, what's new
green? Oh, shit. I can't hear
you. Oh, cool. So, Chad, how
you all doing? You having a
Um, I won't leave you alone. Oh, here you go. Here's Ryan. Why am I looking at your chin?
Because I'm a big got a problem with this chin. I don't have a problem with this chin
I just would rather see his eyes and you know
Like his eyes bitch
Your green eyes
It is cool. Hey guys, I want I need to make I need to I need you guys to come together because you're both cult members
I can't have cult members fighting because
That is what it's not good. We're called we're all cultists together. Okay?
The dog can we have a group hug?
Let's put your arms
I don't hug I don't hug bald people. Just give the middle of us. Okay. It's okay. We're both
I don't hug bald people. Okay. I'll just give her a hug. Okay. Okay fine. Yeah. Yeah, I hug psyche though.
I'm sorry. Are you trying to lick his bald head? Look over my eyes guys. They look green. They are. Good job. Your eyes are also green. Yes.
Here's the best news today. I think Bita said she would never did a green-eyed person or blue-eyed person
She would just date a brown-eyed person. Look how your eyes think of this brown dark brown
You know you won my pole. I mean I put today who shouldn't be to end up with as a city partner
I put Alexandra thing that is
I think I put day one and Christine
You know one
I guess I did. You said I won. You won my landslide actually. I apparently won alexander's pole too for the same basic thing
your men different
Yeah, well, but it mean that I mean
How perfect is it not only did you win the two poles for your eyes are brown?
You're the full. Yeah, the full package, sir. Yeah
But you know what my eyes are dark brown
Don't they be the please rain rain. No, don't they what trouble don't they be that she's trouble. Let's do that
It's what are you talking about? I'm not gonna date be down. I'm not gonna date anybody like online here
Don't worry about it. I am worried about it because you know I worry about you because you know what you deserve a good
It's like there's ever since I met you. I want you to have a pussy to lick
I
Want you I want I would make you happy. I see you with your bald head in there. Yeah
Yeah, I've wanted that since before I met you anyway, so okay. Okay. I'm sorry. This is much before I went too far
How do you know that I'm not already interested in someone and that's why I'm not
Are you looking at other girls? How do you know that's not the case?
Are you or you're not?
I'm just asking how do you know that that's not the case?
Because you would have been bragging about it.
You would have heard about it already.
Oh, Bita, fuck you. I have a hot girlfriend.
I wouldn't do that.
Okay.
But thing it is here's what I want for you. I'm gonna make a toast. I propose a toast the thing that is
Look at my drink. Thing it is. I wish you happiness health well and
Pussy a pussy to lick every night. No, no, no, no, no, it's a it's a mango harder lemonade. I'm drinkable
Thank you for the best wishes
That is doing it. That's probably the nicest thing I've ever said to anybody in my life, you know
Cheers everybody. Hey, I do like this guy. I do like doing this. Oh, there's some Noel's in the chat
No, well come up here and tell us the story of Brandon Q and he's sexually harassed
Chanel is calling me tan daddy now
You yeah, you
You're ugly. I know, right?
Not ugly. He's very good looking.
He is. Have you ever been sunburned on your bald head and appealed?
Yeah. Once, when I went to...
You could see the 10 on his bald head.
When I went to the races at Mostport, yeah.
I was out in the sun all day. It was blazing hot in the middle of August or something like that.
I have a question for the guest backstage.
You promise to behave yourself on my show and I'll let you up. Can you give me a thumbs up like this thumbs up?
Okay, we have a guest coming in
What's up?
Hi, how are you all? I know I'm good. I know I feel bad because you know other people
I'll let you in there showing stuff, but I have seen you misbehave on a show and you must be able to mind
But I know you won't like you promised you wouldn't right?
Yes, and who is this this girl? This is rain and that's rain and that's mr. Rain. Yeah
we have a
Discord
She doesn't give a fuck you're not man
And have you ever seen the mr. Clean commercials we have to clean here tonight. He lost some weight, but he's way
Do you we do you remember me?
Yeah, I do. You were at JC's.
Yeah, and Rain, are you okay with me?
Yeah, why wouldn't I be?
I was just making sure.
Oh, no, you're in a safe place. I'm not going to let anybody pick on you.
As long as you behave, I'll make everyone else do, okay?
Okay.
What show is that?
Remember you and her we're arguing
Okay, okay, I don't argue with anybody, but what did you so ramp or sorry Noel what happened with the branding queue?
We remember anything would happen
Brandon Q you know Brandon Q that that nerve with the glasses that looks like he's um, yes
Yes, tell the story, please
He want me to take up. Oh my god. Oh, yeah, don't okay. That's enough. That's not we get it
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
Right here is a shit.
How dare you take advantage of me?
I'm excited.
How's your basketball season going?
Well, it's a little bit tough.
I don't think it is.
It's wrong.
Nothing just needed you.
Hey, well, how's your basketball season going?
Is your team winning basketball?
It's over.
It's over?
Do you play any off-season games?
Or do you play any sport off-season, I'm saying?
Soccer?
Crying.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, hold on.
OK, I'm going to drop in.
No, I'll come back later.
I don't know what upset her if it was the brand
and cue or the basketball thing.
Brand and cue upsets everybody, unfortunately.
I didn't want to have to ask about it, but.
He you saw what he said about Alex, right? Um, what happened? Sorry say that again
Brandon Q says something about Alex and and Alex did a show tonight
And she said she loves her favorite streamers. I think she said our beta and Brandon Q
But do you see what he posted about her? That's weird. You see doing he posted about Alex?
No, okay. I'm gonna show you
What happened to Noel?
She was having a hard time dealing with the Brandon Q situation, but so so so so am I I'm still I'm still dealing with the aftermath of this horrible
Person. Oh, I think she's back. Oh, man. You're back. No. Well, she's back. I
Want to show you the um
What was said, okay, so Brandon Q is excited. No, oh
Sorry, it's okay. It's okay. She's she can't she can't deal with it right now
But I want to show you what he said about
Alex yesterday. Oh, she's back there. Let's welcome Noelle
Noelle are you okay? We have an even better guest
Yo, what's up Noelle?
She gonna get her titties out or what? Oh?
SIG I say well, it's not like you're it's not like you're gonna do it for her
What's up, SIG?
What's up eraser rain
Okay, so I want to show everybody what was posted about, you know, apparently she says
he's her favorite male streamer, I guess, but I want to show you what he, okay, Raul's
back there.
I want to show you what he posted.
Well, have you seen this?
What he posted about Alec?
Okay.
He posted.
Who he posted?
There she is in his house, and then he goes.
the
Yeah
Like so like like if psyche had AIDS would you judge him because he has AIDS I don't have
I'm saying if if you did though if you did
Hey, boy
Yeah, no, well, you don't this thing, please
So
Yo, no, oh, you're gonna get your pancake tits out or what?
Jesus Christ